在我们继续之前，这里我要说明下
Before we go any further, I need to
Catherine已经说了
jump in here. Catherine has already said that
刷新按钮只是为了debug
the refresh button is for debugging only, but
那么让我们看看这是为什么。在现实世界
let's look at why. In real life, you
你应该总是将刷新按钮隐藏
should always seek to eliminate the refresh button
一个好App应该像个好管家
from your app. A good app should work
在你想要什么并问出来之前就把东西给你
like a good butler, giving you what you want before you even have to ask for
it.
和保存按钮一样，他们都是历史遗留产物。
Much like the Save button, it's a relic of a
对于我们这些从软驱时代过来的人来说
bygone age. That's the best a reassuring safety blanket for those
这就是一个心理安慰
of us who grew up with floppy disks. With the ability
我们现在有能力运行后台任务或者直接从服务器发送信息
to run background tasks or send messages directly from the server
到我们的App，实在没有必要让用户来
to our app, there's really no reason to force users
手动运行刷新，而是应该让App自己去
to manually hit refresh. But the app is up to date
更新同步云端的信息
and sync with the cloud should be a given. But like
但是就像我们之前说过的，这是为了debug。所以比起输出语句
we said, this is for debugging, so like print line it's
还是加一个刷新按钮更方便。让我们来看看
acceptable for this particular purpose. Let's also take a look at
后台线程的模型，哪些选项是有潜在问题的？
our background threading model, which of the following is potential an issue?